Hi guys
Sorry I had to end the last day. Hey time. What's up? Are you tonight?
Who?
Yeah, so I
Had a pretty fun. Oh
It's a picture. Yeah
guys, yeah
Alright, there's time's picture.
Uh, I'm doing fun little sketches.
I have a bunch, so I can't wait to do some more.
Uh, we'll see who comes on up.
Yeah, but I have fun, uh, I had a fun night because, uh, um,
some friends of mine came over and, um, and she wanted to help clean my kitchen and
My kitchen looks really oh my god the floor looks so good. She's like she got this floor bomb. Oh my god, and then
but you know they he had um
Here they have a DMT vape like if you guys anyone tried DMT
DMT like I was I make it but it was like, you know, I smoke it and it's like, yeah, I get I
Get a nice. Oh my god, like just
What I'm doing. Oh, yeah
Go see
I go stop earlier. Hi. Have you ever done DMT ghosts?
I have
Although once again
Okay, uh, I just can't my link it so
How's everyone doing?
Okay
I'm just gonna pin my link and hey thing that is how are you?
You're your side eye. Is that the side I sign or what are you watching? What are you looking at?
Don't look at me
Don't look at me like that. Hey, yeah
Are we doing guys
Yeah, so anyone do DMC ever you ever do DMT goes
That I have are you have oh, okay, so how was it? What'd you think of it? I
Was a psychedelic experience
Take it like experience. Hey, there's people that talk shit like oh, I took acid before like asses let even that
And like it is intense. I won't lie
but that's like
Like it's like fast enough years when you ride down the road like what the lights goodbye
You're not actually like tripping out. You are tripping out. You're not tripping a hard core. You know what I'm saying
But like I was like DMG bro that that'll take you to another whole another world. You know what I'm saying. Oh, yeah
It was like my my like my TV my TV like I was watching music
Oh different music videos were like looking like oh my it was like everything was crazy
And then it's like in the TV like her took up my whole but it just like appeared to take up my whole wall
And I was in the high school. That's why I found out about liars. They said I took acid and I tripped out so bad
Yeah, you might I tripped out a little bit with like the lights and stuff
But you never you never experienced nothing like DMT brother
You never or how I lost whatever you want to whatever
You never experienced shit like that. Yeah, I asked it like people lie about acid all the time like I went to another world
I mean
Maybe but like it's not it's nothing on that. Yeah, it gave me it just gave me like a little like
You know, you get a little like no
You see when you do ask you see like a little light big little streaks
You're like whoa, it's like and the lights look a little bit brighter and stuff, but hey, I have to do one thing
We're back once again
Don't leave me up here with myself. I got to entertain these people that don't like me
Okay, thank you for the claps. Thank you for the clap
My job, that's a weird name. Okay. It's like a week. Oh, thanks for coming back, brother
Yeah, I'm back
Well, what I didn't in future respect I would join your panel again
If you ever have to leave should I just enter like entertain the chat? Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, I trust you to do that brother. You're you're
channel
Appreciate that brother. You know, and I never heard your channel. I know
I'm I debate and shit, but you know
I'm never gonna try to you because you know that cuz I what do I always say do us do us
You know, I never actually try to hurt that, you know, I know I know you
Sometimes you know, it's like because I can actually when you get to know you you're a good guy
I think you know, my you might figure the first time I met you I've been
little fucking
Little degenerate heart. You might be a good guy to you. Oh, thank you. And that hey that my day that's as working, brother
I've been saying that for this by like my third day now. When you get that I
Got this
About a month ago. I got a month here. It might be that you're slicking my hair back you brother
Thank you. Yeah, I saved. Oh, yeah
Thank you. I think a shower is there
my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my god my
Oh, yeah, and they slipped that hair back. You should slip that hair back brother. You're putting it to the front now
Slick it back brother. Oh
My god, oh my god
Hey, you just went up two in the fucking one through ten you just went up two and one point fire, but that's an improvement brother
Thank you at least at least an eight. I'll tell you
Well, I have this open. I haven't been drinking it for a couple hours. He'd left his beer
Harder ice her I see it's pie strawberry pineapple
Alright, I did fuck black cherry. I don't fuck that shit at all
But do you see my drawings I did some drawings of people in the chat
Did you show it last night or do I just hit him today you want to see him? Do you want to see him?
Oh, show him. Yeah, show him. Okay, so here's DJ Electra
Good boy, that's good
Long fucking neck, but that's good. Yeah, that's good. Did you know Gotti? You know Gotti the Gotti?
Alright, alright
Damn you're thinking about everybody in the chat, buddy
Yeah, I don't think you ever you don't got it. And then you know rope you know Robo nomad
He's also
Yeah, he's big nice, you know, you know one for me. I will I will but I don't know what you look like
Okay, could you and here you have you seen easy? I said I do one easy. Do you don't see easy? You see it? Yeah, go ahead
That looks like 420. That's a good one. I did one of JT. Do you know JT? The Wolfman?
I do not know. I don't think I do. I might talk to you. I did one of JT, the Wolfman.
I did one of JT.
Oh, the wolf, you should have said
Wolfman. Yeah, Wolfman.
And then, that's a good deal.
Dingle in the chat. Ask me to do
Dingle. I don't know if you know
Dingle in the chat. Here's, I did
Dingle's avatar. That looks like
Dingle. Oh, hey, whoa.
What was at the bottom of that?
It says 666. Oh god.
Okay, and then we have
That was good though. Yeah
You know sassy scarlet in the chat, you know sassy scarlet from the chat
I'm pretty sure I probably talk, you know half these people. I probably talk to you. I just don't know
I got I got a mess of sassy scarlet
You know, she's wearing like a little cute cow cow girl hat and like she's a cowl girl
But look here as well. This is sassy scarlet guys
Yeah, I put glasses on
That's good
Did you time in the chat, you know, do you know time he's like the here's time. This is time in the chat
Three of them guys. There you go. Not too bad, huh?
Like it how are you gonna draw me to sleep? Are you just gonna leave it blank and be like, oh, hey guys
You know, do you know, um, just a spunky your spunky goes from last night?
Hey, it's funky
Let me see it. I might remember it might remind me of it
Yeah, I remember that yep, I know actually there's about four girls actually that look like that last night
That's funky. Oh double page. Let's go
Because I actually
I know there's like a little jar jar of binks right there because I accidentally wrote pu
Yeah, don't talk shit about jargon. You know, he was he was actually a Sith Ward. Did you know that? Okay?
No, I just remember he was like considered like one of those annoying Star Wars characters all the time
There was a conspiracy theory that came out that he was actually like a Sith Ward. Believe it or not
Okay, okay, so I'm gonna draw
But if you're not in this starboard store, then there's no reason I made it
Oh, excuse me
Where's my pen I need to find my pen and I can draw you I want to draw a
You have to we have to say the gift to say the the magic words. Please draw me like one of your French girls
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I'm buying another pant. Let me see if I can. Oh, yeah. Oh shit. Okay. By the way, so if we ever get stranded on the Titanic
Your your ass is going in the water by the way. I'm going on that door. You're
Okay
Tell me like one of your friends girls if you don't mind. Okay. I'm trying it. Let me see if this works. Oh, here it is
Okay, okay
Okay
So, can you draw Louie Anderson?
Yeah, I can draw Louie Anderson, too.
Okay, so, okay, I'm gonna draw a ghost.
Can you put the word dumb dumb in there if you don't mind?
Yes, even if it's a blank page and it says dumb dumb, that sounds like ghost
I don't smile while you draw my picture
Okay, okay
Here, oh, are you ready guys?
There you go
Go, oh, you left hey page page. I'm doing I'm doing drawings. I did dj Electra and some other people. Oh, you see dj Electra's
It kind of looks like you a little bit though the dj Electra, but yeah
Again, I gave her kind of tube tube. I gave it. It's perfect. She's wearing a she's like very large bosom
but I don't know if I did a great job with her, but
Impage yeah, and I did other people but um, okay, so I got she goes where'd you go?
Oh here is I revealed to ghost like ghost. I want you to react. Are you here?
Ghost oh shit ghost ready. Yeah, here's yours. Okay ready
Beautiful
It's a dumb dumb beautiful
It's a ghost
It looks like you
beautiful
I'm trying to like drug go see it kind of like a like a like a weird head. You might as well sign that shirt
Okay
And you know you just who should buy it as Alexander
beautiful
Hi
Hey, see it's her okay. Oh, I sort of they go. Yeah, do the work. Would you like to buy my picture?
Yeah
Yeah, he said
Listen I got kicked for that too on porch. There's no
That's one of the only rules
Okay, well, my mistake someone said that in the chat man
Because some other bastard said some bullshit no I'm just
I don't want you to get kicked. That's why I'm telling you that's all that's all
Dude that's talking he can say the other guy has to go though
You just said that hard ER word
What's not my panel